A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004) FA482
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2004.053: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2002; AC.2004.053; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3669, R3670; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3669, R3670
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.053.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97001 #540 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR LIAO YU-CAI, 1997-2001 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #544 - CENTRAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FOOD CROPS - RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FOOD CROPS BIOTECHNOLOGY (INDONESIA) - RICE BLAST RESEARCH, 1996-2002 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #552 - INDIRA GANDHI AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GALL MIDGE RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1996-2004 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #553 - INDIRA GANDHI AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR SANJAY K. KATIYAR, 1996-2002 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #559 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - DOUBLED-HAPLOID AND RECOMBINANT-INBRED RICE POPULATIONS, 1997-2001 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #566 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR INDER SINGH SHEORAN, 1997-2002 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #575 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR MANCHIKATLA V. RAJAM, 1997-1998 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #585 - SOUTH CHINA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - RFLP ANALYSIS IN RICE GENE TAGGING, 1993-2000 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #590 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RFLP MAP FOR RICE, 1990-2000 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97007 #26 - BRAZILIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ENTERPRISE (EMBRAPA) - GENETIC DIVERSITY OF CASSAVA, 1996-1999 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97001 #597 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - RICE PLANT REGENERATION, 1989-2002 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97003 #20 - UNIVERSITY OF HOHENHEIM (GERMANY) - STRIGA HERMONTHICA RESISTANCE FROM TEOSINTE TO MAIZE, 1997-2000 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97003 #25 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE AND LIVESTOCK DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - MALAWI MAIZE PATHOLOGY PROJECT AND RESEARCH ACTION PLAN, 1997-2002 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97005 #95 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - ELECTRONIC ACCESS TO FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY, 1997-2000 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97006 #28 - MCINTYRE, BEVERLY D. - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES, 1995-2002 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97006 #29 - GILBERT, ROBERT A. - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES IN MAIZE IMPROVEMENT IN MALAWI, 1995-2002 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97009 #10 - CHINA - AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - JATROPHA CURCAS AND RURAL ENERGY SERVICE NEEDS, 1998-2002 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97009 #6 - UNIVERSITY OF HOHENHEIM (GERMANY) - COOKING STOVE FUELED BY PLANT OIL, 1997-2001 (Box R3670)
    - RF 97012 #147 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - PANEL STUDY ON POPULATION PROJECTIONS, 1998-2001 (Box R3670)
- AC.2004.057: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2003; AC.2004.057; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3671, R3671A, R3671B, R3672; 4 standard record storage boxes, R3671, R3671A, R3671B, R3672.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.057.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 97013 #16 - UNION FOR AFRICAN POPULATION STUDIES - GRANTS PROGRAM FOR RESEARCH ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1990-2001; 3 folders. (Box R3671B, Box R3671A)
    - RF 97013 #16 - UNION FOR AFRICAN POPULATION STUDIES - GRANTS PROGRAM FOR RESEARCH ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2001; 5 folders. (Box R3671B, Box R3671A)
    - RF 97016 #187 - STATUE OF LIBERTY ELLIS ISLAND FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION ON JAPANESE INTERNMENT DURING WORLD WAR II, 1997-1998 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97018 #18 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - ROLE OF RACE, SPACE, AND SKILLS IN EMPLOYERS RELOCATION, 1997-2001 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97018 #19 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN (MADISON) - LOW-WAGE LABOR MARKET AND YOUNG, LOW-SKILLED WORKERS, 1997-2001 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97021 #62 - JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR (ISRAEL) - 19TH JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR, 1999 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97022 #276 - KUBOTA, SHIGEKO - VIDEO INSTALLATION, "HOSPITAL PROJECT", 1998-2002 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97022 #286 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - PRESERVE AND EXHIBIT VIDEOTAPES FROM NATIONAL CENTER FOR EXPERIMENTS IN TELEVISION, 1996-2002 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97022 #292 - BAXI, KADAMBARI - " GLOBAL VARIABLE," WEB SITE EXAMINING GLOBAL EFFECTS OF AMERICAN TV WORLD NEWS, 1999-2002 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97023 #321 - NEW ARTS FOUNDATION - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "KUTTUMPALAM", 1997-2001 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97024 #71 - COMMUNICATING FOR CHANGE (NIGERIA) - INTEGRATED AFRICAN COMMUNICATIONS PROJECT, 1998-2000 (Box R3671)
    - RF 97034 #803 - MAUMBE, BLESSING - ADIA: ECONOMICS OF SMALLHOLDER COTTON PRODUCTION AND PESTICIDE USE IN ZIMBABWE, 1999-2003 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97025 #41 - SOUTHWEST EDUCATIONAL DEVELOPMENT LABORATORY - TEACHER DEVELOPMENT SYSTEM IN SAN ANTONIO INDEPENDENT SCHOOL DISTRICT, 1998-2000 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97025 #43 - INSTITUTE FOR RESEARCH AND REFORM IN EDUCATION - SOCIAL CHANGE AND INSTITUTIONAL REFORM INITIATIVES, 1998-2002 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97026 #7 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - IMPACT OF INFRASTRUCTURE PROJECTS AND COMMUNITY ECONOMIES, 1997-2000 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97026 #9 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - METROPOLITAN SOLUTIONS TO URBAN AND REGIONAL PROBLEMS, 1997-2001 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97033 #68 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - PHSWOW: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, 1997-2000 (Box R3672)
    - LTL Nairobi, 2004.057.001; 1 Item(s) CD-R
    - RF 97033 #69 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF PREVENTIVE MEDICINE - COMMUNITY HEALTH CARE TRAINING IN CHINA, 2001 May (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #806 - AFFUL-KOOMSON, TIMOTHY - ADIA: IMPLICATIONS OF TROPICAL TIMBER CERTIFICATION IN GHANA, 1999-2001 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #810 - BABOU, CHIKH ANTA MBACKE - ADIA: ROLE OF EDUCATIONAL PRACTICE IN THE GENESIS AND DEVELOPMENT OF MURIDIYYA, 1999-2000 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #812 - CHIPOMA, CORNELIUS - ADIA: REFORMING PUBLIC INSTITUTIONS IN ZAMBIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #817 - MONTET, C. SENEWA - ADIA: "DIETARY INTAKES AND SELECTED BIOMARKERS OF CHRONIC DISEASE RISK AMONGST THE MAASAI IN KENYA", 1999-2002 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #819 - GAYATRI, SETHI - ADIA: FEMINIZATION OF THE INFORMAL SECTOR IN BOTSWANA, 1999-2000 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #825 - ODONGO, E. NICHOLAS - ADIA: LIVESTOCK'S CONTRIBUTION TO PHOSPHORUS CYCLING IN KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3672)
    - RF 97034 #827 - GUMBO, DAVISON J. - ADIA: SOCIALIZING MIOMBO ECOLOGY, 1999-2001 (Box R3672)
- AC.2004.061: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2004; AC.2004.061; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3673, R3674.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3673, R3674.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.061.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97034 #832 - RATSIMBAZAFY, JONAH HENRI - ADIA: RESPONSES OF RUFFED LEMURS TO HABITAT DISTURBANCES IN MANOMBO, MADAGASCAR, 1999-2002 (Box R3673)
    - RF 97035 - HUMAN RIGHTS WATCH - ARMS MONITORING UNIT, 1992-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3673)
    - RF 97035 - HUMAN RIGHTS WATCH - ARMS MONITORING UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994 (Box R3673)
    - RF 97036 - FEDERATION OF AMERICAN SCIENTISTS FUND - BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS CONFERENCE, 1991-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3673)
    - AH 9928; RF 97055 #132 - POINT COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORP. - SECOND SOUTH BRONX THEATER FESTIVAL AND CONFERENCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97045 #74 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - WEST AFRICAN YOUTH INITIATIVE, 1999-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97047 #137 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS - SIERRA LEONE CHAPTER - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1998-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97047 #146 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS OF ZAMBIA - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1999-2001 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97047 #147 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - WORKSHOP TO REVISE PROPOSAL ON WOMEN'S SCIENCE EDUCATION, 1999-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97047 #151 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS (KENYA) - OPTION PAPERS ON STRATEGIC RESOURCE PLANNING PROJECT, 1999-2003 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97047 #154 - IOWA STATE UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON PARTICIPATION OF WOMEN IN BASIC AND APPLIED SCIENCES IN AFRICA, 1999-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97049 #2 - URBAN INSTITUTE - NEIGHBORHOOD CONDITIONS AND RESIDENTS' HEALTH AND EMPLOYMENT PROSPECTS, 1998-2002 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97055 #131 - APPALSHOP - "RESPIRITING ART/RESPI RITING COMMUNITY" INITIATIVE, 1996-2004 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #55 - SPACE ONE ELEVEN - PARTNERING IN BIRMINGHAM CITY CENTER THROUGH THE ARTS, 1998-2002 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #56 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - LOOKING IN/TO THE FUTURE PROJECT, 1996-2002 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #57 - WING LUKE MEMORIAL FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY-BASED PLANNING PROJECT AMONG PAN-ASIAN AMERICAN GRASSROOTS ORGANIZATIONS FOR PERMANENT EXHIBITION, 1998-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #58 - LABOR COMMUNITY STRATEGY CENTER - "MAKE HISTORY: BUS RIDERS ACT", 1998-2000 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #59 - APPALSHOP - SOUTHWEST VIRGINIA COMMUNITY FORESTRY INITIATIVE, 1999-2002 (Box R3674)
    - RF 97057 #60 - YOUTH FOR SOCIAL CHANGE - "BEYOND BORDERS" PROJECT 1998-2, 001; 2004 (Box R3674)
- AC.2004.065: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2003; AC.2004.065; 13.1 Cubic Feet 10 standard record storage boxes, R3675-R3684.; 10 standard record storage boxes, R3675-R3684.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Adelman, Janet), 1998-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Ahmad, Perveen), 1995-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Ahmad, Sayeed), 1995-2002 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Andres, Jo), 1998-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Armus, Diego), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Austin, Larry), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Baker, Jean H.), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Barr, David), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Barr, James), 1998-2000 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Barrett, David Marshall), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Beaglehole, Robert) (CO-RESIDENT: Bonita, Ruth), 1998-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Beliaev, Leonid Andreevich), 1997-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Benedikt, Michael L.), 1997-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Bergmann, Barbara Wiggins) (CO-RESIDENT: Helburn Suzanne), 1997-2002 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Berman, Larry), 1997-2001 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Bertelli, Sergio), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Bhatt, Anil Harilal), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Black, Maureen), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Black, Robert Edward), 1997-2001 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Bolt, Christine), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Boone, Joseph A.), 1997-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Boyle, Alan E.), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Boyle, James D. A.), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Brigham, David R.), 1998-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Broadstock, Brenton Thomas), 1997-1999 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Cai, Dorothy Liang-yu) (CO-RESIDENT: Liang, Mao-chun), 1996-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Chisholm, Sallie Watson) (Penny), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Chong, Ping) (COúRESIDENT: Verburg, JoAnn), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Cladis, Mark S.), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Clarke, George Elliott), 1997-2002 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Clarke, Martha) (CO-RESIDENT: Ehrlich, Gretel), 1997-1998 (Box R3675)
      Scope and Contents note
      Cancelled.
    - RESIDENT (Connell, Dan), 1997-2001 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Costonis, John J.), 1995-1998 (Box R3675)
    - RESIDENT (Couto, Walter), 1994-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Covey, Rosemary Feit), 1998-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Croze, Harvey) (CO-RESIDENT: Reader, John), 1997-2000 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (D'Amato, Paul), 1997-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Deere, Carmen Diana) (CO-RESIDENT: Leon, Magdalena), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Demeulenaere, Carl), 1998-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Denoon, Donald John Noble) (CO-RESIDENT: Smith. Philippa), 1998-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Dummett, Michael), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Engelstein, Laura), 1995-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Everett, Steven), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Ezenwa-Ohaeto), 1997-2003 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Feinstein, Elaine), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Gaffney, Edward McGlynn, Jr.), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Garilao, Ernesto D.), 1997-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Gibson, William C.), 1998-2002 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Gilson, Ronald J.), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Goldstein, Inge F.) (CO-RESIDENT: Goldstein, Martin), 1997-2002 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Golubev, Genady Nikolaevich), 1997-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Greaves, Richard L.), 1997-2002 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hall, Bronwyn Hughes), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hanning, Robert W.), 1996-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hansen, Karen Tranberg), 1997-2002 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hashimoto, Eiji), 1997-2000 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Herbert, T. Walter), 1997-2003 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Higham, John), 1997-2002 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hillerbrand, Hans J.), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hillgarth, Jocelyn Nigel), 1997-1999 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Hirschfeld, Thomas J.), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Ho, Fred Wei-han), 1996-2000 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Howard, Maureen), 1997-1998 (Box R3676)
    - RESIDENT (Huang, Shu-Li), 1997-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Intebi, Irene V.), 1998-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Jech, Thomas), 1997-2003 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kaes, Anton), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kelley, Mary), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kellner-Heinkele, Barbara) (CO-RESIDENT: Landau, Jacob), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kennedy, William J.), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Koenig, Barbara Ann), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kornblum, William), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Kudat, Ayse) (CO-RESIDENT: Lacava, Gloria), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Lee, Kwang-Kyu), 1997-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Lenzer, Gertrud), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Levine, Suzanne Jill), 1993-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Lewis, David Carleton), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Ling, Amy), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Litwack, Leon F.), 1997-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Lock, Margaret), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Lolas, Fernando), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (London, Edwin), 1997-1999 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Mahowald, Anthony P.), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Mahowald, Mary Briody), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Makepeace, Anne A.), 1997-2001 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Mann, Thomas E.), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Marcus, Steven), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Mayer, Ann Elizabeth), 1996-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (McCutchan, Ann), 1995-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Mickelson, Roslyn Arlin), 1996-2000 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Morris, Benny), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Negroni, Maria), 1997-1998 (Box R3677)
    - RESIDENT (Newman, Simon P.), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Ohnuki-Tierney, Emiko), 1997-2003 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Okafor, Chinyere Grace ), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Osserman, Robert), 1998-1999 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Papaj, Daniel Richard), 1998-1999 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Paredes Polack, Cecilia), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Perlis, Vivian), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Pollak-Eltz, Angelina), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Quarry, Neville David), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Radin, Beryl A.), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Rattner, Henrique), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Reise, Jay), 1997-1999 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Richardson, Philip L.), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Roemer, Michael A.), 1997-2001 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Ross, John A.), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Ryskulova, Jarkyn M.), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Saha, Lawrence ) (CO-RESIDENT: Biddle, Bruce J.), 1997-2003 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Santos, Ramon Pagayon), 1997-1999 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Shalvi, Alice), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Sharan, Yael), 1996-2000 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Sims, Andrew Charles Petter), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Sirisena, Wanninayake M.), 1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Skogan, Wesley G.), 1997-1999 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Smith, Huston), 1997-2001 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Squier, Joseph), 1997-1998 (Box R3678)
    - RESIDENT (Tatarczyk, Tomas Leszek), 1997-2000 (Box R3678)
    - CONFERENCE: Antibody Consortium for Reproductive and Sexual Health, 1995-2000 (Box R3679)
    - CONFERENCE: Biological Nitrogen Fixation: The Global Challenge and Future Needs, 1995-1998 (Box R3679)
    - CONFERENCE: Blood Transfusions and AIDS, 1995-2004 (Box R3679)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - CONFERENCE: Building Civil Societies: Investing in Foundation-Like Organizations, 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - CONFERENCE: Building Cooperation among Media Policy Research and Advocacv Centres, 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - CONFERENCE: Distrust, 1996-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Tave, Stuart M.), 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Thornton, Leslie) (CO-RESIDENT: Zweig, Ellen), 1997-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Toker, Leona), 1997-2001 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Valjarevic, Srdjan), 1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Van Zile, Judy), 1997-2002 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Vauchez, Andre), 1996-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Verba, Sidney), 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Weissmann, Gerald), 1997-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Welcher, Dan E.), 1993-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Wetherill, Peter Michael), 1996-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Wiebe, Robert H.), 1997-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Wiesenberg, Menachem), 1997-2000 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Williamson, Alan), 1997-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Wilson, Richard), 1995-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Wyner, Yehudi), 1997-2004 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Zabuzhko, Oksana), 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Zenck, Martin), 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Zhang, Hongjun), 1997-1999 (Box R3679)
    - RESIDENT (Zuckerman, Michael), 1997-1998 (Box R3679)
    - CONFERENCE: Domestic Roots of Proactivist Non-nuclear Policv: A New Approach to Non-Proliferation, 1996-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Donors to African Media, 1997 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Early Modern History and the Social Sciences: Brandel's Mediterranean Fifty Years After, 1996-2002 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Economic Costs of Inequality, 1996-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Emerging Infections Surveillance, 1995-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Emerging Infections Surveillance - Supplementary Material, 1995-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Environmental and Global Finance: A Planning Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Ethnic Conflict in the Post-Industrial World, 1996-1997 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Field Staff Meeting, 1997 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Future of Work, 1994-1998 (Box R3680)
      Includes 1995 Conference
    - CONFERENCE: Future of Work - Supplementary Material, 1994-1998 (Box R3680)
    - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogue on Equitable Access to Quality Education, 1996-1998 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Global Health Watch, 1998-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Health 2001, 1996-1998 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Hepatitis Viruses and Human Liver Disease, 1997-1998 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Improving the Quality of Civil Justice Reform, 1996-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Independent Funders: Facing Europe's Immigration and Migration Challenge, 1994 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: International Health for the 21st Century, 1996-1997 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: International River Basins Under Stress, 1995-1997 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Justice in Transition, 1996-2001 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Latin America and the World Economy in the 19th and 20th Centuries, 1996-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Liszt and the Birth of Modern Europe, 1997-2003 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Literary Cultures in History: Reconstructions from South Asia, 1996-2003 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Managing Agricultural Research in Africa, 1997-1998 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: National Support for International Agricultural Research, 1997-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: New Frontiers in Middle East Security, 1995-2001 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: New Perspectives on Film and Television Training for Develooing Countries, 1996-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: 1998 Staff Retreat (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Permanently Unconscious Patients, 1993-2001 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: PharNet: Establishing International Cooperation in Pharmacology Teaching on the World Wide Web, 1997-1999 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Places of Power in the Early Medieval West, 1997-2001 (Box R3681)
    - CONFERENCE: Principles of Sustainable Development Performance Measurement, 1995-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Public Trust and Governance in the Trilateral Democracies, 1997-2000 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Public/Private Sector Collaboration in Contraceptive Research and Development, 1996-1997 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Rebuilding a Democratic Burma, 1997-1999 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Role of Medical Abortion in Developing Countries, 1997-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Second International Meeting on the Modulation of Arthropod Vector Competence, 1994-1996 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Social Approaches to an Industrial Past, 1995-1999 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Towards Collaborative Peace: The Control of Small Arms and the Reversal of Violence, 1996-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Towards Justice: Implementing Human Rights Protections in the Middle East and North Africa, 1996-1999 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Towards Policies for Conservation and Sustainable Use of Aquatic Genetic Resources, 1997-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Transport and Trafficking in the Malaria-infected Erythrocyte, 1997-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Unaccompanied Refugee Minors: Issues in Repatriation, 1996-1999 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: UNAFPA Special Advisory Group to the Executive Director, 1997 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Using Strategic Communication to Advance Female Education in Africa, 1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Words and Voices: Critical Practices of Orality in Africa and in African Studies, 1995-1998 (Box R3682)
    - CONFERENCE: Worldwide Perspectives on Women and Gender, 1997-2002 (Box R3682)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.065.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97057 #62 - ESPERANZA PEACE AND JUSTICE CENTER - ARTE ES VIDA PROJECT IN SAN ANTONIO, 1997-2002 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #606 - RF 98001 #606 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RICE GENES RESEARCH, 1984-2002; 2 folders. (Box R3683)
    - RF 97057 #65 - PROJECT ROW HOUSES - ARTISTS' RESIDENCIES AND INSTALLATIONS IN HOUSTON, 1999-2002 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #620 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MAP-BASED CLONING OF TUNGRO RESISTANCE GENES IN RICE, 1997-2002 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #621 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - INSECT RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1996-2002 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #635 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - TWO-LINE HYBRID SYSTEMS FOR RICE, 1997-2002 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #638 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY (NEPAL) - CHARACTERIZATION OF NEPALESE RICE BLAST POPULATIONS, 1997-2001 (Box R3683)
    - RF 98001 #645 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - INTEGRATED RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY IN THAILAND AND SOUTHEAST ASIA, 1992-2002 (Box R3684)